[{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980276307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":19892,"timeElapsed":64660},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980286306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":9994,"timeElapsed":74659},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4550,"timeElapsed":79213},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980294013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3147,"timeElapsed":82366},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980299295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5278,"timeElapsed":87648},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980306842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":7542,"timeElapsed":95194},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980312697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":5848,"timeElapsed":101049},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980318918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":6218,"timeElapsed":107271},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980325515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":6594,"timeElapsed":113868},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980336731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":9390,"timeElapsed":125083},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980343970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":7234,"timeElapsed":132323},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3489,"timeElapsed":135818},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980350510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3041,"timeElapsed":138863},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980355490,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4977,"timeElapsed":143843},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980359941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4447,"timeElapsed":148293},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980364705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4760,"timeElapsed":153058},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2197,"timeElapsed":155259},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980373155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6245,"timeElapsed":161507},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980378686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5527,"timeElapsed":167039},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980385999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5854,"timeElapsed":174351},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3389,"timeElapsed":177746},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980391663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2265,"timeElapsed":180016},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4107,"timeElapsed":184128},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2727,"timeElapsed":186860},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980403057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4545,"timeElapsed":191410},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4002,"timeElapsed":195416},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4412,"timeElapsed":199833},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2440,"timeElapsed":202276},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980422702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7133,"timeElapsed":211055},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980425261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2553,"timeElapsed":213613},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980428545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3280,"timeElapsed":216898},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434586,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6038,"timeElapsed":222939},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4874,"timeElapsed":227819},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980443497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4028,"timeElapsed":231850},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":6771,"timeElapsed":238625},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980453223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2945,"timeElapsed":241575},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2879,"timeElapsed":244458},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980458258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":246611},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":5526,"timeElapsed":254073},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2138,"timeElapsed":256216},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3235,"timeElapsed":259454},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3244,"timeElapsed":262702},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980476819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2467,"timeElapsed":265172},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3528,"timeElapsed":268705},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1965,"timeElapsed":270673},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4372,"timeElapsed":275049},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980489383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2683,"timeElapsed":277736},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":7686,"timeElapsed":286939},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2320,"timeElapsed":289262},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4026,"timeElapsed":293291},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2758,"timeElapsed":296055},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3461,"timeElapsed":299520},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3668,"timeElapsed":303193},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":305236},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3296,"timeElapsed":308536},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1878,"timeElapsed":310419},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7277,"timeElapsed":318861},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980532798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2286,"timeElapsed":321151},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980535842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3042,"timeElapsed":324195},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3265,"timeElapsed":327464},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3025,"timeElapsed":330493},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2740,"timeElapsed":333235},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1763,"timeElapsed":335001},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1597,"timeElapsed":336605},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980549627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1369,"timeElapsed":337979},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":19490,"timeElapsed":358865},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2096,"timeElapsed":360964},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3271,"timeElapsed":364240},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980577924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2033,"timeElapsed":366277},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980580659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2731,"timeElapsed":369012},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2477,"timeElapsed":371493},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1876,"timeElapsed":373372},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980586962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1938,"timeElapsed":375315},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980588610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1643,"timeElapsed":376962},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4536,"timeElapsed":383042},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2168,"timeElapsed":385212},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3452,"timeElapsed":388668},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2694,"timeElapsed":391367},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2526,"timeElapsed":393899},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3053,"timeElapsed":396956},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2036,"timeElapsed":398996},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2789,"timeElapsed":401788},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615284,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1846,"timeElapsed":403637},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":7687,"timeElapsed":412613},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980626049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1784,"timeElapsed":414402},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2915,"timeElapsed":417320},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980630466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":1494,"timeElapsed":418819},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2724,"timeElapsed":421546},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2524,"timeElapsed":424074},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1844,"timeElapsed":425923},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1862,"timeElapsed":427787},{"subjectID":"x3klql923z","prolificID":"6754ba11bbb6e43e6bdfdfd8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26491b8365842b540d5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2695,"timeElapsed":430486}]